Life has a price.
Hidden Away is a mystery, drama, thriller film directed by Peter Sullivan.
A woman and young daughter escape her abusive husband by faking their deaths.
Eight years later she is happily living in the upscale Palm
Springs with her now-17-year-old daughter.
When her husband discovers they are still alive, he tracks them down and spies on them to
learn all about the new life they've created until he can exact his revenge.
Alexandra / Stephanie, played by Emmanuelle Vaugier.
Andrew, played by Ivan Sergei.
Brett, played by Sean Patrick Flanery.
Lynn, played by Elisabeth Röhm.
Rachel, played by Allie Gonino.
Amy, played by Hallee Hirsh.
The Hidden Face (Spanish: La cara oculta) is a 2011 thriller film
directed by Andrés Baiz, who also co-wrote the screenplay.
The film is a Spanish-Colombian co-production.
It stars Quim Gutiérrez, Clara Lago and Martina García.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.